<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Priyadarshini Engineering College</string>
    <string name="about_pec">Priyadarshini Engineering College, the flagship of Jai Barath Charitable Trust, was established in 1995 at Vaniyambadi in Vellore district of Tamilnadu The college has been approved by All India Council for Technical Education, New Delhi and affiliated to Anna University, Chennai. Priyadarshini Engineering College situated in the rural area of Vaniyambadi, Vellore District is committed to the vision of developing itself into a multi campus, Inter - disciplinary Institution of Excellence through symbiotic efforts and innovative practices of management and faculty to provide the student with an ambient academic environment, ideal for the pursuit of knowledge and development career. </string>
    <string name="motto">Perseverance, Endurance, Commitment </string>
    <string name="about_developer">This Android Application is Designed and Developed by "<b>Mohammed Rehan</b>". Am a Tech Enthusiastic Programmer who is passionate about writing codes and building apps. This app serves as a platform for Priyadarshini Engineering College students to make right use of the college and to utilize all the opportunities during college life. With the help of this application, students can keep themselves updated with the newsfeed happening inside the college campus in just one click. Students can also download notes of their respective departments and can manage their time table effectively. \n\n  \" I am inspired by those who have the courage to do things that have never been done before things that were believed to be impossible \" - Sandeep Maheshwari \n\n This is what inspired me to develop this app for PEC which no one has ever think of it or done it before in our college. I believe anything is possible if you are crazy enough about your goal with a never give up attitude. \n\n "<b>BEST OF LUCK ENGINEERS!!!</b>"</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Priyadarshini Engineering College \n Chettiyappanur \n Vaniyambadi - 635751 \n Tirupattur District \n Tamil Nadu \n Website : www.priyadarshini.net.in \n Phone : 04174-227591 \n Mobile : 9047583337 / 9047666423</string>
</resources>
